In this video, we are going to discuss the
stock of ICICI Lombard General Insurance. If we talk about the current price of the stock, then the
current price is 120.80. If we talk about the 52 week
high, then it is
1486.40 and its 52 week low is 1000 seventy
van. See friends, the video is going to be very short
and important, so stay tuned till the end of the video. So
let us now move on to
its technical chart. This chart that you are
seeing, I have opened it on the Trading View
website. If we talk about the time frame, then
we have set it in the ODI time frame. If you look here,
after hitting a high of 1360 on almost 17 August 2022,
we saw continuous selling in it.
Even before, after reaching this level, the stock had gone
up by taking support from here
and exactly when it came here, it went
up from here and after that,
here also you can see that again it rose
from this support.  It is going up taking support,
now see this zone here is a very sharp
support zone, the
stock has formed multiple times before as well, that is why
we can see it bouncing upwards, so
now see this pattern is forming here, so
due to this its level here,
this pattern is complete, its pattern is complete almost
above 278,
so almost these levels here
can come in it and here we will
also talk about the neck line, so we have seen a breakout above the neck line as well,
see
friends, this video has been made only and
only for educational purposes, so
in this video no suggestion of buying or selling any stock is being
given, so let us now go to
its tigrative website and
check from there its overview for cast
and what advice do the analysts give us about wine,
now we have come to the tigrative website,
after searching the name of the company in the search box on the
left side, the name of the company will be shown to you and
below it its current price will also be shown, if we
talk about current price then let us talk about its current
price  If we look at it, the
stock appears to be giving better returns than the Bank of
India. If we
talk about Deedan, it is
not that attractive.
Friends, at this point, you
consumers, Rock is not in the overbought zone. This
means that you
can buy from here because the
stock here is not in the overbought zone. The most
important thing is that it is
showing negative flex. Whenever you
make an entry in any stock for short term,
long term or swing, you
make an entry only after seeing the breakout flag.
This company is a large cap company. So let
us now check
what its financial trend is showing in the last four years. We are showing the
data of the last four years from 2019 to 2022. If we
talk about the growth of the company, then
we are seeing very good growth of the company year after year.
Due to this, we may see
good levels in the stock in the coming few days. So,
let us now
check what its forecast analyst tells
us.  Sala de bank,
before moving ahead in the video, I would like to tell you one thing
friends, many such videos have been uploaded on our YouTube channel,
if you have
not seen those videos then
definitely watch those videos as well and if you have
not yet subscribed to our YouTube channel
then subscribe to the channel and
also press the bell icon so that
updates of upcoming videos reach you
and now let us check its
forecast,
as you can see here, 24
analysts are advising 70% buying,
which is quite good, you
can consider it, friends, this
video has been made only for educational purpose,
whenever you
make an entry in any stock, then make the
entry only after consulting your financial advisor once
and you should take the decision on your own, so
let's meet in the next video
with this YouTube channel, till then take
care